abc-of-yoga.com 2005-12-20

# Privacy Statement @ ABC-of-Yoga.com

|   Yoga Info  
---  
 Yoga Information |   
 Practicing Yoga |   
 Yoga and Health |   
 Yoga Props |   
 Other Yoga |   
 Yoga Shop  
 Yoga Tools |   
 Yoga Resources |   
 Yoga Paraphernalia |   
 Yoga Travel  
 Travel Services |   
 World Destinations |   
 Partner Program |   
  |   
     | 

* * *

Print   

As a visitor of one of our websites you are given the opportunity to become a member and benefit of the extra features we offer to members. Becoming a member is done by filling out a registration form and by submitting this form your details are stored in our member database. Becoming a member is free and voluntary. In this section we will outline how we collect personal information and how personal information is protected and used by us. 

## What personal information do we store?

Our registration form asks for personal details. Some of the questions asked are mandatory, others can be left blank. Upon registration you will have to submit the following details: 

  * First and Last name
  * Date of birth
  * Country
  * Email Address

Some of our websites enable members to register directly for courses and workshops that we offer and host ourselves. On those websites you will have to register with a valid telephone number as well. This to ensure that we can reach you both by email and phone should there be cancellations or changes in the course/workshop program or details.

All personal information and account settings are stored in our database. Only certain ABC Group administrators have access to this database and this database is not made public or shared with third party companies. 

## What is personal information used for?

We gather your personal information for the following purposes: 

  * In case of websites where we offer courses/workshops, personal information is used to send confirmation emails, course details and reminders. 
  * Sending out our newsletter. Members can decide for themselves if they want to receive our newsletter or not. 
  * Personal Information is used in member profiles which are linked to possible article and/or comment submissions on our website. In this way visitors can see who submitted what.
  * We do not share our member database with third parties nor do we make email addresses or other contact information available through our website or otherwise. We do not send out unsolicited email.

## Third Party Advertising

We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php). 

## Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. If you have any questions about our membership program or this Privacy Statement please Contact Us |      |  |     Article Options  
---  
|  |  | Comment on Article  
---|---  
| Email this Article  
| Printer Friendly  
   Member Login  
|  Username:   
Password:   

 Login   
  Password?  

Do you know much about Yoga?

Join us today and we will give you the tools to share your Yoga knowledge with the whole world!

  Become a Member    
  
   Yoga Travel  

Do you provide any Yoga related Services?

Join our Travel Partner Program and Present your Services on this Yoga Portal absolutely for Free!

   Advertisements  
|  Advertising Info   
|
